Woody Woodpecker Goes to Camp is a family, comedy
film directed by Jonathan A. Rosenbaum.
After getting kicked out of the forest, Woody thinks he's found a forever home at
Camp Woo Hoo — until an inspector threatens to shut down the camp.
Woody Woodpecker (voice), played by Eric Bauza.
Buzz Buzzard (voice), played by Kevin Michael Richardson.
Wally Walrus (voice), played by Tom Kenny.
Angie, played by Mary-Louise Parker.
Zane, played by Josh Lawson.
Maggie, played by Chloe De Los Santos.
Woody Woodpecker Goes to Camp is a 2024 American live-action animated slapstick comedy film directed by Jon Rosenbaum (in his feature directorial debut) and
produced by Jon Kuyper, from a screenplay written by Jim Martin, Cory Edwards, and Stephen Mazur, and a story conceived by Mazur and Edwards.
The film is based on the cartoon character of the same name and serving as a standalone sequel to the 2017 film
Woody Woodpecker and the second installment of the Woody Woodpecker live-action film series.
The film was produced by Universal 1440 Entertainment and with Universal Animation
Studios and distributed by Netflix, where it was released on April 12, 2024.
The film explores themes of camping, woodpecker, bird.
The tone is lighthearted.